From what I was able to find, this demo was released in limited quantities, only in Japan at concerts.
I'm only providing this rip because of the difficulty of finding a copy on the market (and even then the band wouldn't get any money from the sale).
Sorry for the really low quality scans of the album art, but some of them are low quality prints to begin with and I don't have that great of a scanner (they're all cut off on the left edge a bit).

Keep on enjoying きのこ帝国!
-chocolatekake